http://www.niagaraswim.org/team/eznslsc/page/governance/coppa-policy

Site MapContact Us
Facebook
Twitter
Sign in
HomeNewsHelp WantedCoach RecognitionCovid-19 UpdatesCalendar2020 - 20212020-2021 Observed and ApprovedCalendar ArchiveMeet HierarchyGovernanceAbout Niagara Swimming LSCPermanent OfficeBoard of DirectorsCommitteesGovernance DocumentsConflict of Interest FormMeeting MinutesSpring HOD AgendaFall HOD AgendaBid Calendar & InfoLocal ClubsMembership StatusClub StatisticsPosting PolicyCOPPA PolicyTimesCurrent Meet ResultsMeet Results ArchiveTime StandardsSwimming RecordsTop 10 ListsClub RecognitionSwim GuideMembership FormsMeet ManagementBid Calendar and InfoFinancial ManagementClub StrengtheningZone Team InfoInsuranceUSA Swimming Report of OccurrenceUSA Swimming Racing Start CertificationCoachesOfficialsExternal LinksDiversity & InclusionDisabilityUSA Swimming Pool CertificationSafety Certification Training ProvidersSafe SportOperational SafetyZone TeamDocumentsMembership Info and Registration FormsCoaches InfoOfficials InfoNiagara Officials TeamAppHall of FameDisability InfoDiversity, Equity, and Inclusion InfoUSA Swimming Deck PassAthlete WellnessAge Group SwimmingAge Group PhilosophiesAthlete KudosImportant Dates and DeadlinesCamps & Clinics2021 Season Programming OptionsMeet Progression Pyramid
Niagara Swimming COPPA Statement
http://niagaraswim.org is a general audience website. While we encourage members to browse our website, we also wish to educate parents and children about issues of privacy when visiting our site. As a result, we are committed to full compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and the USA-S Swimming Privacy Policy. COPPA applies to individually identifiable information about a child that is collected on line, such as full name, home address, email address, telephone number or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child. The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) is the enforcing authority.    Information gathered by Niagara Swimming Niagara Swimming does not gather or store personal information about athletes on its website. Information acquired during registration for swim meets is the property of USA Swimming and its use is within the control of USA Swimming. USA Swimming strictly limits the use of member’s personal information to that information necessary for the conduct of the business of USA Swimming and its LSCs. Niagara Swimming adheres to COPPA through the following: ·        Limited advertising permitted on our website, subject to Niagara Swimming’s posting policy. Click here to see Niagara Swimming's posting policy. ·        There is no collection of personal information on the website that includes athlete’s full name, home address, email address, or telephone number that would allow someone to identify or contact a child. ·        Niagara Swimming tracks usage statistics on its website through Google Analytics, we do not track information linked to individuals who visit the web site. ·        Access to private information on the website is controlled by limiting the staff and Board members with administrative access to Niagara Swimming’s website. ·        Limited pictures of children are allowed on the website and Niagara Swimming’s social media sites (Facebook, Twitter). o    Niagara Swimming obtains a signed release from parent/guardians if children are singled out in any way or a picture is obtained from a non-public event or setting. o    Pictures from Niagara Swimming public events may be published, but at no time is a child identified by other than a first name; team caps are blurred when possible; Niagara Swimming complies with suggested Federal guidelines to limit identifiable markers in photographs so there are no more than 3 markers. o    News items may be shared from other sources with different policies. Requests for removal may be sent to [email protected].
o    Parents may request that any posted photograph or any other information that they feel is too identifiable be removed from the Niagara Swimming website. o    Children’s information is never shared with third parties (other than USA Swimming).
Third-Party Sites and Sponsors Our site contains limited links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices, which may differ from ours.
Cookies and How We Use Them Cookies are used to gather basic tracking information and to monitor the presentation of advertisements and are placed on your hard drive by many major websites. Niagara Swimming does not intentionally use cookies on its website; however, the site is powered by TeamUnify, which does collect some information as identified in their privacy statement.
CLICK HERE to go to the FTC website and learn more about COPPA.
CLICK HERE to learn more about USA Swimming's Privacy Policy.
CLICK HERE to read TeamUnify’s privacy policy.
Please contact Niagara  Swimming's General Chair at [email protected]  with any questions or concerns.
Our Mission: Supporting strong clubs, building stronger swimmers by providing opportunities from novice to elite.
Our Vision: Inspiring swimming for generations.
© Copyright SportsEngine, Inc. This website is powered by TeamUnify but is owned by and subject to the Organization’s privacy policy.
© Copyright SportsEngine, Inc. This website is powered by GoMotion but is owned by and subject to the Organization’s privacy policy.
Privacy Statement
